http://www.nrpt.co.uk/legal.htm

Search
Home / Legal terms and conditions
Legal Terms And Conditions
The use of this website, provided by Thehealthfinder Holdings Limited T/A NRPT.co.uk is governed by the following terms and conditions for it's use.
By accessing or using the NRPT.co.uk website (therein referred to as the "website"), you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions of use. These may be changed at any time by NRPT.
It is of the utmost importance for us at NRPT.co.uk to ensure that this, and every subsequent visit you make to our web site, is with complete peace of mind. You have every right to trust and to expect confidentiality, and it is our duty to respect this right.
Personal Privacy
Your privacy is our priority. As such, we believe you should have an unrestricted view into how we collect data about the people who visit our site - yourself included - and what we do with that data.
Third Parties Privacy Practices
We do not share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not supply any identifiable personal information to third parties outside what an NRPT member adds to their personal profile. For example, we provide equal opportunity information as regards our users, but we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Our intention is never to use or share personally identifiable information provided to us in ways that are different than the ways described above without also providing you with an opportunity to "unsubscribe" or prohibit such unrelated uses.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site please get in touch or send your mail to :
Thehealthfinder Holdings Limited
73 Barton Road
Barton Seagrave
Northamptonshire
NN15 6RS
Copyright Warning
Users and other website owners may copy some material for personal use only. Under no circumstances may any content, copy or other data (including images) be republished or reproduced either on another website or as part of any commercial service, without the prior written permission of NRPT.co.uk.
As a company, NRPT.co.uk take this very seriously and will pursue all breaches of our copyright through the appropriate avenues.
Trademarks
All page headers, logos, custom graphics and button icons are service marks and trademarks of NRPT.co.uk. All other trademarks, product names and company names or logos cited anywhere on any of the above websites are the property of their respective owners.
Conditions of Use
NRPT.co.uk endeavors to ensure that all information is correct at the time of publishing, but does not accept any liability for error or omissions.
Information provided the websites is not written to meet individual requirements and does not constitute business, medical or other advice which you can rely on. It is not a substitute for professional advice from your business, medical or other professional adviser who you should consult in all cases to determine whether any information provided is relevant to, and appropriate for, you.
NRPT.co.uk does not necessarily endorse and product or service mentioned.
NRPT.co.uk is accordingly not responsible or liable for any loss, damage, expense or injury to any person resulting from any use of, or reliance on, any information provided.
NRPT.co.uk is not responsible for information that has been presented by any individual or company in respect of their NRPT member profile. We do everything to ensure that any membership information (Exercise Register or CIMSPA) is correct and not expired, but this is the responsibility of the trainer to inform the NRPT.co.uk of any changes.
NRPT.co.uk reserves the right to prohibit abusers of the site and its contents and to terminate any accounts this user might have. Abuse would include things like acts which violate the law, threatening, abusive or harassing or vulgar materials, transmission of viruses and other nasties, transmission of junk or spam mail, advertising and endorsement of products or services without NRPT.co.uk permission, and attempts to collect or store personal information about other users of the websites.
As an NRPT.co.uk member, you are solely responsible for any and all information that you distribute in any way ('Your Content') using your profile and our website. You are also responsible for any consequences that may result from "Your Content". The NRPT.co.uk does not review and has no obligation to monitor any content that you display, especially if that content is inaccurate, whether knowingly placed that way or not.
NRPT.co.uk has the right to refuse and remove any content uploaded, posted, or distributed using the websites, including any of Your Content. NRPT.co.uk may also retain Your Content and disclose Your Content (including the contents of your private communications):
if required by law
to properly operate and maintain the websites
in connection with any claim that Your Content violates the rights of any third-party
to protect itself, its officers, directors and employees, the users of the websites and the public
to enforce these terms and conditions
By providing Your Content through any publicly accessible areas of the websites or submitting any of Your Content to the websites, you automatically grant to NRPT.co.uk a perpetual, royalty free, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from and distribute such of Your Content into any form, medium or technology now known or hereafter developed. In addition you waive any and all moral rights in such of Your Content.
By providing Your Content through any publicly accessible areas of the websites or submitting any of Your Content to NRPT.co.uk, you warrant that Your Content is not subject to any third party copyright or any other proprietary right and that you have full capacity and authority to make such posting, transmission, distribution or submission.
External Links
All of NRPT.co.uk websites provide links to external websites and the facility to search the web using an automated system. These links and search results are included to give you the opportunity to explore an issue or topic in more depth. NRPT.co.uk is not responsible for the content of these Internet sites and your use of them is governed by their terms and conditions.
Tweet
Trainers
PT Courses
Search Nationwide for Personal Trainers and Fitness Courses
Hundreds of Personal Trainer Courses & Fitness Courses Across the UK
Aberdeen
Aberystwyth
Aldershot
Alsagers Bank
Altrincham
Andover
AOL
Armagh
York
Other Readers Like...
Guides
International Society of Sports Nutrition Releases Position on Energy Drinks
Ian Duncan
Guides
Why Interval Training Is Essential for Fat Burning
Ian Duncan
Guides
Why Bother with Winter Training?
Ian Duncan
Guides
Leafy Greens Help Prevent Damage Caused by Physical Training
Ian Duncan
Search By› City› Town› CountyTraining Courses› Online PT Courses› Full-Time Courses› Distance LearningPopular Pages› Training Courses in London› London Personal Trainers› Training Courses in TownsQuick Links› Advertise with Us› Legals› Contact Us
